https://www.thewhippet.net/privacy-policy.html

TheWhippet.net
Discover the Perfect Dog Breed
Menu
Whippets 101HomeWhippet InfoWhippet TraitsNutritionHealth and CareClubs & ActivitiesWhippet FAQ
Puppies and RescuesBulletin BoardWhippet PuppiesBreedersWhippet RescuePuppy NamesWhippets in Italia
TrainingWhippet TrainingBehavior Problems
Whippet GearWhippet CoatsBest CollarsBedsWhippet Books
Your WhippetDog of the Day!Whippet ManiaYour StoriesYour PoemsWhy a Whippet?Your VideosAdoption StoriesMemorials
GalleryWhippet PicturesWhippet MixItalian GreyhoundsGreyhoundsMore Hounds
AboutFreebies!My DogsDrop Me a Line!What's New
Do you have a whippety question? Enter here your query or keyword.
will help you make an informed decision about sharing
personal information with us.
Use of Cookies and Web BeaconsA cookie is a string of information that TheWhippet.net stores on your computer, which your browser provides to TheWhippet.net each time you return to the site. We use cookies to help us identify and track visitors, their use of our website, and their website access preferences.TheWhippet.net uses Google Analytics to analyze the use of this website. Google Analytics collects demographic and interest data, and generates statistical and other information about website use, by means of cookies. These cookies are kept on your computer. We share this information with Google, which will store and use this information on its servers. Google's privacy policy is available here.TheWhippet.net uses information from Google Analytics to track the number of visits to the website, browsers and operating systems. No personally identifiable information is obtained from these cookies. We use the information that Google Analytics generates relating to our website to create reports about the use of the site. These reports allow us to update the site and improve your usage of it.If you do not wish your data to be collected via Google Analytics, you can install its opt-out browser extension or add on here. Advertising CookiesWe use third-party advertising companies (AdSense, Amazon and Media.net) to serve ads on our website. These companies use cookies and web beacons in their ads to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement.We share this information with these companies, but do not provide them with any personally identifiable information for cookie or web beacon use, so they cannot personally identify you with that information from our website.You may opt out of personalized ads for over 125 different ad networks.  http://www.aboutads.info/Some third-party advertisements are served by Google. Google's cookie enables it to serve ads to our visitors based on their visits to other sites on the Web.You may opt out of personalized ads by visiting the Google advertising privacy policy. This link from Google provides more information about how Google manages data in its ad products.A few ads on this site are served by Media.net Affiliate Products and ServicesWe receive an affiliate commission for some of the products/services sold on TheWhippet.netThe affiliate services platforms we use are Amazon and SBI (SiteSell).By clicking on a product or service link, you consent to that platform's use of cookies, as outlined in the link below. The Privacy Policies for each of our Affiliates are listed below.Amazon Privacy PolicySBI (SiteSell) Privacy Policy  Sellfy Privacy PolicySocial MediaOn this website there are links to Facebook, Pinterest, Instagram, Twitter, and YouTube. When you click on them or leave a comment, your browser connects directly with that site and sends information such as your IP address, the date and time of your visit and information about how you use the social site.We use AddThis to facilitate social sharing.  This service collects information such as how often our material is shared to various social platforms.  You can read their privacy policy here. Should you wish to prevent those platforms from collecting data, please view their individual policies by using the following links:YouTube (Google) Privacy Pinterest Privacy Policy Instagram Privacy Policy Facebook Privacy Policy  Twitter Privacy Policy  If you use these platforms, you may also want to view and adjust your privacy settings if needed.TheWhippet.net uses Facebook pixels to determine the effectiveness of some Facebook ad campaigns. You can change your Facebook ad settings here.Refusing CookiesYou can set your browser to accept or refuse all cookies automatically or notify you when a cookie is being requested. Taking this action should not cause a problem with the continued use of our site. Consult the Help section of your browser for guidance on how to refuse all cookies or to notify you when a cookie is requested.If you choose to refuse TheWhippet.net's cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the site.Personally, Identifiable InformationTheWhippet.net may collect and use your personal information for the following purposes:
To run and operate our site.
To display content on the site correctly.
To improve customer service.
To help us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
To personalize your user experience.
To understand how our users as a group use the services and resources provided on our site.
To improve our site.
To improve our products and services.
To run a promotion, contest, survey or other site feature.
To send information to you that you agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to you.
To send periodic emails, which may include electronic newsletters and/or autoresponder series of emails.
To respond to your enquiries, questions, and/or other requests.
TheWhippet.net may collect personally identifiable information from you in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when you visit our site, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our site from time to time.Specifically, if you subscribe to our newsletter, we will ask for your first name and will require your email address.If you complete a form, we will require your name and your email address, and will ask for information relevant to the purpose of the form.If you submit content to us, we will ask for your name and location. Photos you include with your submission, or details in your submission, may personally identify you.If you request to be notified about comments on any content you submit to us, or request to be notified when others submit content, we will require your first name and your email address.This site also uses Facebook commenting. Facebook stores all your comments and may show them on your timeline, depending on your Facebook settings.You can always refuse to supply personally identifiable information and visit our site anonymously. However, it may prevent you from engaging in certain site-related activities.If we make material changes in the collection of personally identifiable information, we will inform you by placing a notice on our site. We will use personal information received from you for internal purposes only and will not sell it or provide it to third parties.We also collect each visitor's IP address, which helps us combat spam and fraud. We do not use IP addresses for any other purpose.Non-personally Identifiable InformationWe may collect non-personally identifiable information about you whenever you interact with our site. Non-personally identifiable information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about your method of connecting to our site, such as the operating system and the Internet service provider you used, and other similar information.Children's Online Privacy Protection ActThis website is directed to adults. It is not directed to children under the age of 16. We operate our site in compliance with current regulations. Anyone under the age of 16 must have parental consent to use this site.We do not knowingly collect or use personally identifiable information from anyone under 16 years of age.Release of InformationIf we sell TheWhippet.net, the information we have obtained from you through your voluntary participation in our site may transfer to the new owner as a part of the sale so that the service provided to you may continue.In that event, you will receive notice through our website of that change in control and practices, and we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the purchaser honors any opt-out requests you might make.Data StoragePersonally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information collected by this site is stored on our host's servers. That host is SiteSell Inc., located at 1000 Saint-Jean Boulevard, Suite 702, Pointe-Claire, QC H9R 5P1 Canada.If you wish to review your information stored on the SiteSell servers for TheWhippet.net, click on this link.You can also edit, download or delete any of your information from the servers by clicking on that link.How You Can Correct or Remove InformationWe provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our commitment to protect your personally identifiable information. If you have submitted personally identifiable information through our website and would like to update that information or have it deleted from our records, click on this link.Updates and Effective DateTheWhippet.net reserves the right to make changes in this policy. If there is a material change in our cookie and privacy practices, we will indicate on our site that those practices have changed and provide a link to the updated privacy policy.We encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will know what information we collect and how we use it.Agreeing to TermsIf you do not agree to TheWhippet.net's privacy policy as posted here on this website, please do not consent to the setting of cookies and the collection and storage of your personally identifiable information.Your explicit consent indicates acceptance of this privacy policy in its entirety.Last updated: June the 6th 2018
Back to Homepage
Whippet TrainingProblems and Solutions
Help your whippet become a perfect companion.Solve behavior problems like mouthing, separation anxiety and car sickness, with simple methods.Find out how to get your puppy ready for leash walking, coursing and showing.
Whippet TailsHound stories and pics
Enjoy whippet stories and hound watercolors in an easy to read format.
Whippet Freebies!Find out how to house train your puppy in no time with these free instructions, plus a handy infographic as a welcome gift for your subscription to The Whippeteer, our free newsletter!Don't worry your Email is safe with us, subscribe now!
Email
I am at least 16 years of age.
I have read and accept the privacy policy.
I understand that you will use my information to send me a newsletter.
Subscribe
Free Whippet Puppy Tips!
Are you planning to get a whippet puppy? Have you just got one? Start on the right foot with these tips!Subscribe in the box below  and get the installments of my flash course  directly in your mailbox for free.This invaluable course is concise but covers all the basics of getting ready for a puppy. It's divided in 3 short chapters that cover: finding a puppy, shopping list, choosing a puppy and first days at home.You'll receive them every 3 days to let the information sink in and allow you to get it all organized and ready for your new puppy.
Find your Whippet!Check out our FB pagesWhippet Rescue Whippet Pups
Whippets 101HomeWhippet InfoWhippet TraitsNutritionHealth and CareClubs & ActivitiesWhippet FAQPuppies and RescuesBulletin BoardWhippet PuppiesBreedersWhippet RescuePuppy NamesWhippets in ItaliaTrainingWhippet TrainingBehavior ProblemsWhippet GearWhippet CoatsBest CollarsBedsWhippet BooksYour WhippetDog of the Day!Whippet ManiaYour StoriesYour PoemsWhy a Whippet?Your VideosAdoption StoriesMemorialsGalleryWhippet PicturesWhippet MixItalian GreyhoundsGreyhoundsMore HoundsAboutFreebies!My DogsDrop Me a Line!What's New
Bourbon the Whippet Wins Reserve Best at 2020 Westminster Show!
Westminster Dog Show 2019Hound Group
Hounds atCruft 2019
TheWhippet.net - All Rights Reserved Copyright © 2007-2018The Whippet.net does not endorse any  dog breeder, including those listed on this site. These listings are provided only for the convenience of our visitors and are not paid ads. TheWhippet.net does not sell dogs and makes no guarantee to the value or health of any dog. TheWhippet.net declines any responsibility for transactions between seller and buyer.  Click here for our Privacy Policy
